Sanjeev Bhasin is seen trading 140 points higher,
welcoming the year. Hello,
tell me like a machine, where is the focus and trend? It is a wicket-
style day. I
think that writing and acting is on the
table right now. If not today, then tomorrow you will fast for 15 days.
And momentum is good in the industry because
the data, macro data is gold.
Corporate results, you have seen from
IT from Bank HDFC Bank will come up
with the best profit saver on the 17382. And
today it is large cap day for you. So in the last step,
I will just tell you about
Reliance HDFC Bank. Maruti, today I will
give you news that Maruti will
invest Rs 18,000 crore in the next five years
and will produce 10 lakh vehicles and he himself is in
laughter Vijay Upper Zomato. He will give multiple for
sending food to homes. Over ten five year
multiple Maruti, so if you have this running plant, then
my first pick is unquestionably
Maruti 73. Take ₹100. Vacancy vision, if you want to
sell them in the next year, then
you can imagine vision 7373.  In the state,
take Maruti stop loss of 71981 70610,
second by way Kaya HiC
Jhalawar which I am very bullish on Vikram Auto
Centre good record also share and General
Insurance World Mobiles at 1540 42,
take stopped for 1505 target more than fixed
update, if it does not run today but in the
second you midcap banks will definitely run, you
just do Bandhan Bank RBI and IDFC,
first you are seeing ladies in Bandhan,
target of 314 15 to 11 325 Chowkpur, it will
go to 345 in the month of July, Bandhan RBL Bank
IDFC year and 22 midcap IT will be the
best performer in the year internship TDS,
let us see good momentum intense in front of you